hello thank you for coming here today my
你好，谢谢你今天来我这里
name is Jo Darcy I work in Oracle's Java
我叫乔·达西（Jo Darcy）
platform group and I'll be speaking
平台小组，我将发言
today about JDK 9 language tooling and
今天有关JDK 9语言工具和
library features in case we don't have
库功能，以防我们没有
time for Q&amp;A at the end of the talk if
谈话结束时进行问答的时间是否
you tweet at this hashtag JDK 9 lying
您在此标签JDK 9上发布了推文
tools libs I can answer questions there
工具库，我可以在那里回答问题
the last slide of the talk will also
演讲的最后一张幻灯片也将
have a URL to the PDF of the slide deck
有指向幻灯片平台PDF的URL
so this is Oracle's safe harbor
所以这是甲骨文的避风港
statement it lets you know you shouldn't
声明它让你知道你不应该
put too much trust in what I have to
对我必须做的事过于信任
tell you here today especially regarding
今天在这里告诉你，特别是关于
Ford looking statements however since
福特寻找声明，但自
the talk is about JDK 9 + j TK 9 gist
演讲是关于JDK 9 + j TK 9要点
ship there aren't very many
船不是很多
forward-looking statements in this talk
本演讲中的前瞻性陈述
it might get a bit repetitive seeing
可能会有点重复
Oracle safe harbors statement throughout
Oracle安全港声明全文
the conference
此次会议
if you want some tips for alternative
如果您需要一些替代技巧
safe harbors in the area I'll be happy
我会很高兴在该地区的安全港
to provide those afterward a quick
为以后的人们提供快速
survey before we get started which JDK
在开始使用哪个JDK之前进行调查
train are you using in production are
您正在生产中使用的火车
there any very early adopters on JDK
JDK上有非常早期的采用者
nine yet
九点了
I'll let's understand well how about
我会好好了解
who's downloaded the JDK 9 JDK alright
谁下载了JDK 9 JDK好
that's good maybe some more people after
很好，也许之后会有更多人
the talk or after the talks at the
演讲或演讲结束后
conference will download it JDK 8 in
会议将在其中下载JDK 8
production alright almost everyone JDK 7
几乎每个人都可以进行生产
alright about a quarter did ek6 one or
好吧，大约有四分之一的ek6还是
two stray hands now now we're all
现在有两只流浪的手
friends here so who who will admit to
这里的朋友，谁愿意
using JDK five or older in production
在生产中使用5或更高版本的JDK
still all right a few honest people in
还好吧，一些诚实的人
the audience yesterday those are great
昨天的观众很棒
releases but we have a main many
发布，但我们有很多
features as since then so hopefully
从那时起，希望如此
you'll be able to try those out soon
您将可以很快尝试
overview of JDK 9 as I mentioned a JDK 9
正如我提到的JDK 9一样，概述了JDK 9
just ship recently a few weeks ago like
就在几周前才刚发货
the last few JDK project it was
最后的几个JDK项目是
developed under the auspices of open JDK
在开放JDK的主持下开发
so if you're interested in participating
因此，如果您有兴趣参加
that development following the mailing
邮件发送后的开发
list trying out the builds you can find
列出尝试找到的构建的列表
more information on the open JDK website
在开放的JDK网站上获得更多信息
throughout this talk I'll be using a
在整个谈话中，我将使用
term JEP JEP is it JDK enhancement
JEP JEP是JDK的增强功能
proposal these are documents we use for
提案这些是我们用于的文件
feature tracking in the JDK and if you
JDK中的功能跟踪，如果您
go to the open JDK page for JDK 9
转到JDK 9的打开的JDK页面
you will see a long list of the Jets
您会看到一长串的喷气机
they're about 90 jets we won't be
他们大约是90架，我们不会
talking about all of them today but
今天谈论他们所有人，但是
besides many jets JDK 9 had many bug
除了许多喷气机外，JDK 9还有很多错误
fixes this is a comparative chart of a
修复这是一个比较图表
number of bug fixes in 9 vs 8 so as you
9 vs 8中的错误修复数量，因此
can see JDK 9 has almost 20,000 fixes in
可以看到JDK 9中有将近20,000个修复程序
it which is slightly less than twice
它略小于两倍
what JDK 8 had so a very large release
JDK 8有这么大的版本
all around including jigsaw
到处都有拼图
functionality and many other features
功能和许多其他功能
we'll be talking about
我们将谈论
so no talk about JDK 9 would be complete
因此，关于JDK 9的讨论将不完整
without some mention of modularity
没有提到模块化
project jigsaw project jigsaw was a very
项目拼图项目拼图是一个非常
large feature and the modularity
大功能和模块化
functionality from jigsaw is to make
拼图的功能是使
programming in the large easier modules
在更简单的大型模块中编程
bun together at one or more packages as
将一个或多个包装包在一起
a unit of reuse and offer it stronger
重用单位并提供更强大的功能
encapsulation than jar files one reason
比jar文件封装的原因之一
jigsaw was a large project was because
拼图是一个大项目，是因为
it required changes throughout many
它需要整个改变
aspects of the platform the language
平台方面的语言
tools and libraries the language changes
工具和库的语言变化
for jigsaw include a new kind of file a
拼图包括一种新型文件
module info Java file which declares
声明的模块信息Java文件
dependencies between modules Java C was
Java C模块之间的依赖关系是
updated to support that new kind of
更新以支持这种新的
source file as well as to find
源文件以及查找
dependencies through modules there are
通过模块的依赖
corresponding updates made to the Java
对Java的相应更新
command and the hotspot run time to
命令和热点运行时间为
understand the modularity restrictions
了解模块化限制
and there were also API changes those
还有一些API更改
API changes include updates to the core
API更改包括对核心的更新
reflection and the language model to
反思和语言模型
model the new aspects of the platform
为平台的新方面建模
now there's much more to be said about
现在还有更多要说的
modularity than can fit in a single 45
模块化，无法容纳单个45
minute session for that reason the
因此，分钟会议
jigsaw team has 5 45 minute sessions
拼图团队有5个45分钟的课程
here at JavaOne some of these have
在JavaOne上，其中一些
already occurred they may be being given
已经发生，他们可能会被给予
again later in the conference so you can
稍后在会议中再次发言，以便您可以
check the scheduling app for that and a
检查调度应用程序和
few other sessions are later this
其他几个会议稍后
afternoon or later in the conference for
会议的下午或以后
this talk we'll start next by talking
这个谈话我们接下来将开始谈论
about our approach to stewardship of the
关于我们的管理方法
Java platform then we'll talk about the
Java平台，那么我们将讨论
tooling language and library updates
工具语言和库更新
while some of those features are pretty
虽然其中一些功能很漂亮
distinct sometimes a feature will
有时会有所不同
involve more than one area and if we
涉及多个领域，如果我们
have time at the end some Q&amp;A
最后有时间进行一些问答
so the stewardship the approach we use
所以管家我们使用的方法
for stewardship for the JDK is very
对于JDK的管理非常
different from the stewardship approach
与管理方法不同
used by say Denethor and their current
由说Denethor及其当前使用
the Kings films who was the steward of
国王电影的管家
gondor the number one goal of the Java
贡多Java的第一目标
platform group for the last seven and a
最后七个平台组和一个
half years has been to keep Java vibrant
保持Java蓬勃发展已经有半年了
part of keeping Java vibrant means
保持Java充满活力的手段的一部分
keeping the things that work today
保持今天有效的东西
working tomorrow
明天工作
so that topic is compatibility so the
这样的主题是兼容性，所以
fundamental policy we have about the JDK
关于JDK的基本政策
is managing compatibility in a sensible
正在明智地管理兼容性
way the general ushion policy is we
我们的一般政策是
don't want to break binary compatibility
不想破坏二进制兼容性
as defined in the Java language
如Java语言中所定义
specification that means we want
意味着我们想要的规格
programmers that link today to be able
今天联系起来的程序员能够
to link tomorrow we want to avoid
链接明天我们要避免
introducing source incompatibilities
引入源不兼容性
that is where programs stop compiling or
那是程序停止编译的地方，或者
if they compile they compile they mean
如果他们编译他们编译他们的意思是
something different and we want to
有些不同，我们想要
manage the behavioral compatibility what
管理行为兼容性
a method does when you call it now this
当您现在调用此方法时
philosophy applies to the API changes we
理念适用于我们的API更改
make in the platform but it also applies
在平台上制作，但它也适用
to the language features we have for
我们拥有的语言功能
instance because of this policy we still
实例，因为这项政策，我们仍然
recognize old version 40 5.3 class files
识别旧版本40 5.3类文件
generated by Java one at Oh over 20
由Java一人在20多岁时产生
years ago we limit the cases where legal
多年前，我们限制了合法的案件
stowed code stops compiling in newer
存放的代码停止在较新的版本中编译
platform releases and we want to avoid
平台发布，我们要避免
changes in the semantics of code
代码语义的变化
generation when recompiling so as with
重新编译时生成
any sort of compatibility policy one of
任何形式的兼容政策之一
the trade-offs here is finding the right
这里的权衡是找到正确的
balance between stability and progress
稳定与进步之间的平衡
so we have three kinds of compatibility
所以我们有三种兼容性
source by any binary and behavior both
通过任何二进制和行为来源
behavioral and if we remember back in
行为，如果我们还记得
physics class we could grab the graph
物理课，我们可以抓图
this is a three dimensional diagram and
这是三维图，
different kinds of releases have
不同类型的发行有
different kinds of compatibility regions
不同种类的兼容区域
that are acceptable so if we take say
那是可以接受的，所以如果我们说
the security update releases those
该安全更新将释放那些
quarterly releases that come out four
每季度发布四次
times a year they have a very small
一年几次，他们有一个很小的
region to make changes there's some
进行更改的区域有一些
behavioral change of course because we
行为改变当然是因为我们
want to fix the vulnerability and maybe
想修复该漏洞，也许
there's a little bit of source
有一点来源
compatibility for a JDK specific API if
是否兼容JDK特定的API
we have a larger release such as the
我们有一个较大的版本，例如
update releases like 8 you xx and 8 u 40
更新版本，例如8 you xx和8 u 40
the
的
was a much larger so they have more room
更大，所以他们有更多的空间
for behavioral change and more
改变行为等等
opportunity to make source changes
进行源更改的机会
however in both of these cases there is
但是在这两种情况下
no room for binary and compatible
没有二进制和兼容的空间
changes we don't want to break people or
我们不想打扰别人的变化或
update release because we want people to
更新版本，因为我们希望人们能够
use those update releases as soon as
尽快使用这些更新版本
they come out for a platform release
他们出来发布平台
like JDK 8 GA or JDK 9 GA the situations
像JDK 8 GA或JDK 9 GA的情况
have been different there's the maximum
有所不同，有最大
amount of rooms make behavioral changes
房间数量会改变行为
and more room to make source changes and
还有更多空间来进行源更改，以及
in exceptional circumstances with enough
在特殊情况下，足够
justification there's even the
证明甚至有
possibility to make some binary
做一些二进制的可能性
incompatible changes I'll mention a few
不兼容的更改，我会提到一些
of those that were made in JDK 9 later
后来在JDK 9中制作的那些
in the talk this is an example that
在谈话中，这是一个例子
helps illustrate the compatibility
帮助说明兼容性
policy and how applies to different
政策以及如何适用于不同
releases so if we look at the
发布，所以如果我们看一下
specification for hash that dot iterator
点迭代器的哈希规范
it says you get back in iterator and the
它说你回到迭代器，
elements are returned in no particular
元素没有特别的返回
order that means according to the
这意味着根据
specification we can change the
规格，我们可以改变
iteration order at any time in any
随时随地的迭代顺序
release and still obey the specification
发布并仍然遵守规范
so how does this change square with the
那么这如何改变与
compatibility policy well this would be
兼容性政策，这将是
a binary compatible change because we're
二进制兼容的更改，因为我们
not altering the set of methods it's
不改变它的方法集
also a source compatible change because
也是源兼容的更改，因为
the compilation of a client doesn't
客户的汇编不
depend on the internals of the method
取决于方法的内部
body so you can change the method body
主体，因此您可以更改主体的方法
and that won't change whether or not the
而且无论是否
client compiles however this is a
客户端编译，但这是一个
behavioral compatibility change and we
行为兼容性改变，我们
know people can in do implicitly and
知道人们可以隐性做
sometimes accidentally rely on the
有时不小心依靠
iteration order therefore this is the
迭代顺序因此是
kind of change that we generally
我们通常的那种变化
wouldn't make an either kind of update
不会进行任何一种更新
release but we would make and have made
释放，但我们会做出并已经做出
in a platform releases and the reason
在平台上发布的原因
we'd make it in a platform release is to
我们会在平台发布中做到这一点
take advantage of say better hashing
利用说更好的哈希
algorithms so this is the terminology
算法，这就是术语
for compatibility just used in the JDK 8
为了兼容JDK 8
and JDK 9 release guides and
和JDK 9发行指南，以及
compatibility documents so I recommend
兼容性文件，所以我建议
you look at those when you look to
当你看着那些
migrate to those those releases so how
迁移到那些发行版，如何
is JDK 9 different JDK 9 follows this
是JDK 9，不同的JDK 9遵循此
same model of looking after
相同的照顾模式
compatibility but to support modularity
兼容性，但支持模块化
a larger compatible
更大的兼容
compatibility impact than usual was
兼容性影响比平常大
allowed include including some notable
允许包括一些值得注意的
behavioral incompatibilities for for
的行为不相容
example if you're using a tool that
例如，如果您使用的是
assumes the existence of RTR you'll have
假设您将拥有RTR
to update to a newer version of the tool
更新到该工具的较新版本
that doesn't rely on that because RTR
那不依赖那个，因为RTR
has gone away it's no longer in the JDK
已经消失了，它不再存在于JDK中
9 image those that information is stored
9图像信息存储
differently to support modularity there
不同地支持那里的模块化
are even a few cases where he broke
甚至有几次他破产
binary compatibility there was an
二进制兼容性
unfortunate dependency between the
之间的不幸依赖
logging framework in between Java
Java之间的日志记录框架
desktop so we don't want to suck in all
台式机，所以我们不想吸
of Java Java desktop anytime you want to
Java桌面随时随地
use logging and we fixed up I getting
使用日志记录，我们修复了问题
rid of these property listener methods
摆脱这些属性侦听器方法
that weren't crucial to the API later on
后来对于API而言并不重要
in the talk are also talking about the
在谈话中也正在谈论
more muscular deprecation policy we have
我们有更强硬的弃用政策
with better tools to manage the
有更好的工具来管理
transition going forward so now we'll
过渡正在进行，所以现在我们将
start talking about some of the tooling
开始谈论一些工具
improvements and the first of those
改进和第一个
tooling improvements is J shell Lisp
工具的改进是J shell Lisp
systems have generally provided a read
系统通常提供了读取
evaluate print loop as the primary way
评估打印循环为主要方式
you interact with that system so you
您与该系统进行交互，因此您
type commands and system evaluates that
输入命令，系统评估
it gets back to you similar
它会回到你类似
functionality is found in Ruby and
在Ruby中找到了功能，
Python and on the JVM ecosystem
Python和JVM生态系统
languages also Scala groovy and closure
语言也支持Scala常规和闭包
so what about Java well now in jdk 9 we
那么现在在jdk 9中Java又如何呢？
also have a rebel and the repple is
也有叛逆者
called j show I'll do a quick demo of
叫j show我将做一个快速演示
that the right window up here
右边的窗户在这里
alright so the J shell is a new command
好了，所以J Shell是一个新命令
in the JDK bin directory so we'll get
在JDK bin目录中，我们将获得
that started here so there are commands
从这里开始，所以有命令
and J show of Eli backslash so we can do
和J显示Eli反斜杠，所以我们可以
help intro as it suggests here and we
帮助介绍，因为它建议在这里，我们
get some guidance on using the tool but
获得有关使用该工具的一些指导，但
if we're using a new language
如果我们使用一种新的语言
environment what's the first program you
环境你第一个程序是什么
want to write hello world so we can just
想写你好世界，所以我们可以
start typing hello world here and we'll
在这里开始输入hello world，我们将
see what happens
走着瞧吧
now we get back hello world now that's a
现在我们回到世界，你好
nice thing to have not not very
好东西不是很
complicated but notice we didn't have to
复杂，但请注意，我们不必
deal with public static void main string
处理公共静态无效主字符串
all those things so if you just want to
所有这些事情，所以，如果您只想
do some informal program and get started
做一些非正式的程序并开始
you can do it right away
你可以马上做
so besides expressions we can define
所以除了表达式我们可以定义
variables in J show so let's say we
J中的变量显示，所以我们说
wanted to find a double variable named
想找到一个名为
tau when you want that to be equal to
tau，当您希望等于
twice pi so we know there is a pi
两次圆周率，所以我们知道有圆周率
constant in the math class so we start
在数学课中保持不变，所以我们开始
typing math we can get autocomplete here
键入数学，我们可以在此处自动完成
these are the alternatives so we can
这些是替代方案，因此我们可以
pick math and then if we look in math
选择数学，然后再看数学
where the variables begin with P we see
变量以P开头的地方
there's pi there and if we hit tab a few
那里有圆周率，如果我们点击选项卡
more times we'll see that we can get the
更多的时候，我们会看到我们可以得到
documentation for pi and we can see it
pi的文档，我们可以看到它
is indeed the constant we're looking for
确实是我们正在寻找的常数
course fields aren't very interesting on
课程领域不是很有趣
the by themselves you also want method
你自己也想要方法
so we can say define a method name
所以我们可以说定义一个方法名
square that takes a double and returns
取双并返回的平方
the square of it
它的平方
in besides Auto completing on elements
在自动完成元素上
of the JDK we can also autocomplete on
在JDK中，我们还可以自动完成
fields and methods we've defined
我们定义的字段和方法
ourselves so we can say take the square
我们自己，所以我们可以说走广场
of the sine of tau autocomplete and we
tau自动完成的正弦
have some command line editing so we can
进行一些命令行编辑，以便我们可以
cut and paste that so if we square the
剪切并粘贴，所以如果我们平方
sign in square the cosine is something
余弦符号是平方
we should get something close to one and
我们应该得到接近一个的东西
that is indeed what we get in this case
这确实是我们在这种情况下得到的
and then we can exit out of the show so
然后我们可以退出演出，所以
going back to the slides here so this is
回到这里的幻灯片，这是
good for students there's less ceremony
对学生有好处，减少了仪式
getting started but J shell is not just
入门，但J Shell不只是
for novice programmers it's helpful for
对于新手程序员来说，这对
experienced programmers too if you want
如果您愿意，也可以是经验丰富的程序员
to start exploring using a new API like
开始使用诸如
the new API is in a JDK 9 I found J
新的API在JDK 9中，我找到了J
shell helpful myself and help publicly
自我帮助并公开帮助
prepare for this and other talks so J
为这次和其他会谈做准备，所以J
shell has snippets those expressions as
外壳具有这些表达式的摘要
well as Java commands the J shell
以及Java命令的J Shell
implementation is interesting it
实现很有趣
leverages many existing JDK technologies
利用许多现有的JDK技术
including the compiler API and the
包括编译器API和
debugger API and there's a user's guide
调试器API和用户指南
to help get started now while we might
帮助我们现在就开始
not have Taco Tuesday at JavaOne we do
我们在JavaOne没有Taco星期二
have J shell Wednesday so tomorrow there
周三有J炮弹，明天在那里
are 4 talks about J shell the first of
是关于J Shell的4个话题的第一篇
these is by Robert field who is the
这些是罗伯特·菲尔德（Robert Field）的
architect and lead engineer of J shell
J Shell的架构师和首席工程师
and if Robert hears you like J shell he
如果罗伯特听到你喜欢J壳，他
might show you how to invoke a nested J
可能会向您展示如何调用嵌套的J
shell from within J shell so you can use
J Shell中的shell，因此您可以使用
a ripple while you're using a ripple so
使用波纹时会产生波纹
and if you don't catch Robert stock
如果你不赶上罗伯特·斯托克
there's other ones to catch here next we
接下来还有其他要抓住的地方
talk about a few changes in Javadoc so
谈论Javadoc的一些变化
for many years a Java doc has output
多年以来，Java文档已输出
HTML 401 a few years ago html5 was a new
几年前的HTML 401 html5是新的
standard and now Java doc has a option
标准，现在Java文档可以选择
to output html5 instead of the older
输出html5而不是旧的
HTML 4.01 and this is the version of
HTML 4.01，这是
HTML we use for the jdk documentation
我们用于jdk文档的HTML
now people might have seen the doc lint
现在人们可能已经看过医生皮棉
checks in JDK 8 these are checks you can
在JDK 8中检查这些是可以检查的
run from Java doc or from Java C to
从Java doc或Java C运行到
validate the Java doc comments
验证Java文档注释
we added some more configuration options
我们添加了更多配置选项
to dockland in particular to select
到码头区特别是选择
which packages you want the checks to
您要检查的包裹
apply to so in the JDK build for
适用于在JDK构建中
instance we primarily checked the Java
我们主要检查Java的实例
and Java X packages because we want the
和Java X软件包，因为我们希望
documentation we published to be free of
我们发布的免费文档
these sorts of problems the document
这些问题的文件
checks range from the syntax of the HTML
检查范围从HTML的语法
tags their semantics and you can enable
标记他们的语义，您可以启用
and disable them individually if you
并分别禁用它们
haven't finished clearing one category
还没有完成清除一个类别的操作
of warnings from your build yet in terms
来自您的构建的警告
of the implementation of the doclet the
doclet的实现
doclet api is very old it leads back to
doclet api很旧，导致返回
or very early jdk s and with the benefit
或非常早的jdk并受益
of hindsight the API modeling the Java
后见之明建模Java的API
language could be improved since the
语言可以改进，因为
doclet API we actually have several
doclet API我们实际上有几个
other reflective api's and the platform
其他反射式API和平台
that are better suited to allow language
更适合允许语言
evolution
演化
so we've reimplemented the standard
所以我们重新实施了标准
doclet on top of a job X Lion Model API
作业X Lion Model API之上的doclet
which is supported in the compiler so
编译器支持
this gives us a better base for a Java
这为我们提供了更好的Java基础
doc improvements going forward another
Doc的改进又向前迈进了一步
feature we have is a javac search and
我们拥有的功能是javac搜索，
I'll go back to do a demo of that
我会回去做一个演示
so this is a download of the JDK nine
这是JDK九的下载
Javadoc there are few changes to notice
Javadoc有几处更改需要注意
one is that it's divided in a few
一个是它分为几个
sections that are just analyzed Java SE
刚刚分析过的Java SE部分
documentation there's also documentation
文档还有文档
for JDK specific classes as well as Java
适用于JDK特定的类以及Java
FX altogether the frames view is still
FX总共仍然显示框架视图
available but it's not the default and
可用，但不是默认值，
if we scroll down we'll see that the
如果我们向下滚动，我们会看到
primary organization is done by modules
主要组织由模块完成
so we have all the Java C modules then
这样我们就拥有了所有的Java C模块
the modules that are in the JDK and so
JDK中的模块等等
forth
向前
and at the top right hand corner we have
在右上角
a search box so let's say we're
一个搜索框，所以我们说
interested in finding more about math
有兴趣寻找更多关于数学的信息
this is a math so we we see here that we
这是一个数学运算，所以我们在这里看到
get back search results over package
通过包获取搜索结果
names as well as type names and field
名称以及类型名称和字段
names and from here we can navigate to
名称，从这里我们可以导航到
those sorts of things now we know in
现在我们知道的那些事情
Java sometimes the names are very long
Java有时名称很长
that that's part of the convention so if
那是公约的一部分，所以如果
we wanted to find say the equals ignore
我们想找到说平等无视
case method that would be a lot of
案例方法会很多
typing but we actually don't have to
打字，但实际上我们不必
type that all out because the Java doc
键入所有内容，因为Java文档
Search reports camelcase sirs so if you
搜索报告驼峰先生，如果您
start typing EQ and then IG we can get
开始输入EQ，然后IG我们可以得到
the equals of North ignore case method
等于North忽略大小写方法
straight away all right we'll go back to
马上好了，我们将回到
the slides
幻灯片
so the implementation is in JavaScript
所以实现是在JavaScript中
in the client so you don't have to go to
在客户中，所以您不必去
the server for that if you wanted to
服务器，如果你想
find your own index terms there's a tag
找到自己的索引词，有一个标签
to allow you to do that as well
允许你也这样做
what it does currently is it indexes
目前它正在做索引
over the names of the you know modules
在您知道的模块的名称上
packages types and fields and so forth
封装类型和字段等
the next two features will are designed
接下来的两个功能将被设计
to ease getting from one JDK release to
简化从一个JDK版本到
another the first of these is cross
另一个，第一个是十字架
compiling with the - - release flag -
使用--release标志进行编译-
Java C so for many years the advice of
Java C这么多年的建议
the Java C mamta age and in blogs i I've
Java C mamta时代以及我写过的博客
written and others have written has been
已写，其他人已写
to cross compile to an older JDK there
交叉编译到较旧的JDK
were three things you needed to do you
是你要做的三件事
have to set the source version to the
必须将源版本设置为
older release the target version at and
较旧的版本在和发布目标版本
finally the boot class path to the older
最后是引导类路径到旧版本
release people didn't always follow this
释放人们并不总是遵循这个
guidance so we get a flow of bugs in
指导，以便我们在
there and we wanted to do something
在那里，我们想做点什么
about that a related policy change was
关于相关的政策变更是
to limit the range of source and target
限制来源和目标的范围
values we support in Java C starting in
从Java C开始支持的值
JDK 8 we don't support all the way back
JDK 8我们一路不支持
to the beginning anymore
从头开始
we support the current release and in 3
我们支持当前版本，并在3
back so in JDK 9 we support 9 as well as
返回，因此在JDK 9中我们支持9以及
8 7 + 6 + 6 is deprecated because we
不推荐使用8 7 + 6 + 6
find to remove that the next time we
找到下次删除它
remove a release and something similar
删除一个发布和类似的东西
will be done for JDK 10 which is
将针对JDK 10完成
probably gonna be called 18 not 3 or one
可能会被称为18而不是3或1
of the subsequent releases now why do
现在的后续发行中，为什么
you need to boot set the boot classpath
您需要启动设置启动类路径
well let's say we have two versions of
好吧，假设我们有两个版本的
the JDK here and there's a library in
JDK在这里，还有一个库
the first version there's a foo method
第一个版本有一个foo方法
that takes a double and then as an
需要一倍，然后作为
optimization in a later JDK release we
在以后的JDK版本中进行优化
had a full through method that takes an
有一个完整的方法需要
integer so that's a perfectly compatible
整数，因此完全兼容
change according to our compatibility
根据我们的兼容性进行更改
policy and let's say we have the client
政策，假设我们有客户
library here that uses foo and we
这里使用foo的库，我们
compile it against JDK n + 1 so which of
针对JDK n + 1进行编译，因此
the two foo methods is the compiler
这两个foo方法是编译器
going to choose for foo 1 2 3 4 it's
要为foo选择1 2 3 4
going to choose the food that takes an
要选择需要
integer that's the most specific food
最具体的食物是整数
version and that's what language
版本，那是什么语言
specifies okay so what happens if we
指定可以，如果我们
take that file compiled against JDK n
将针对JDK编译的文件
plus 1 and we run it against JDK n we'll
加1，然后针对JDK运行它，我们将
get a runtime error or something like
得到一个运行时错误或类似的东西
this no such method error what the
这个没有这样的方法错误是什么
detail message of the error here is
错误的详细信息在这里是
saying the
说
is looking for a food that takes an
正在寻找一种需要
integer but it's not finding one it's
整数，但没有找到一个
not finding one in JDK and because it
在JDK中找不到一个，因为
isn't there there's only a food method
不是只有一种食物方法
it takes a double so this is the kind of
需要一倍，所以这是一种
problem people can run into when the you
人们在您遇到问题时会遇到的问题
don't said the boot class path when you
当你不说引导类路径
cross compile so since we still had this
交叉编译，所以因为我们仍然有这个
problem we talked about am a java c team
我们谈论的一个Java C团队问题
we added a warning if you didn't set the
如果您未设置
boot class path when you the older
年龄较大时引导类路径
versions we did that back in jdk 7 but
版本我们在jdk 7中做了
the problem still persisted and we were
问题仍然存在，我们
talking about on the team and we said
在团队上谈论，我们说
you know what we know what people
你知道我们知道什么人
actually want to do here they just want
其实想在这里做他们只是想要的
to cross-compile to the old version so
交叉编译到旧版本
why don't we just let them do that
为什么我们不让他们这样做
directly instead of having to set these
直接而不需要设置这些
three variables and that is indeed what
三个变量，这的确是
we've done now with the Java C dash -
我们现在使用Java C破折号完成了操作-
release em flag semantically it's
从语义上释放em标志是
equivalent to setting the source and
等同于设置源和
target to the older release as well as
定位到较早的版本以及
the MU class path however the
MU类路径，但是
information about the class path is
有关类路径的信息是
available to Java C so this is shipped
可用于Java C，因此已发货
as part of the JDK in a compressed
作为JDK的一部分压缩
fashion so you don't have to manage that
时尚，所以您不必管理
kind of state to yourself anymore a few
对自己的状态已经不再
advantages of this you don't have to
的优点，您不必
worry about managing those old RT jar
担心管理那些旧的RT jar
files yourself if you use maven plugins
如果您使用Maven插件，请自行归档
like animal sniffer that's meant to
就像动物的嗅探器
prevent using wrong API as you should
应避免使用错误的API
have less need for that
对此的需求较少
another advantage if you're doing this
如果这样做，另一个好处
across compilation is you might be able
跨编译，你也许能够
to take advantage of newer compile
利用更新的编译器
idioms in Java see their bug fixes in
Java中的惯用语可在中查看其错误修复
Java C and sometimes there are very
Java C有时有时
large performance improvements one of
大型性能改进之一
the projects we had in Java C and JDK 9
我们在Java C和JDK 9中拥有的项目
was called tiered attribution which
被称为分层归因
helps speed up type inference in some
在某些情况下有助于加快类型推断
sorts of situations
各种情况
so the steeply rising curve there was
所以那条陡峭的上升曲线是
the JDK 8 runtime in seconds and you'll
JDK 8运行时只需几秒钟，您将
notice it's a log scale so it is getting
注意这是对数刻度，因此
quite slow quite quickly for these very
对于这些非常缓慢的
small programs that we're using type
我们正在使用的小型程序
inference in a particular way so a
以一种特殊的方式推断
straight line on a log scale is
对数刻度上的直线是
basically exponential growth so that's
基本上是指数增长，所以
not very good if you want to have a
如果你想拥有一个不是很好
scalable compiler environment so we want
可扩展的编译器环境，因此我们想要
to do something else so we re-engineered
做其他事情，所以我们重新设计
how inference worked and we got these
推论是如何工作的，我们得到了这些
much faster lines on the bottom so we
底部的线快得多，所以我们
both get that using Jade Java Sea from
两者都从Jade Java Sea获得
JDK 9 and we get that sort of
JDK 9，我们得到了那种
performance using
表演使用
the Java Sea from JDK 9 using - -
使用--从JDK 9中获取Java Sea
release 8 so if your cross compiling to
发布8，所以如果您的交叉编译为
8 you get the benefit of the
8您将从中受益
re-engineering we've done in the newer
重新设计我们在较新的产品中所做的
compiler the next feature is multi
编译器的下一个功能是多
release jar files so it's inconvenient
释放jar文件，这样很不方便
if you want to package up a library for
如果您想打包一个库
distribution to make one version of the
发行一个版本的
library for different versions of the
不同版本的库
JDK so typically you'll compile for the
JDK，因此通常您会为
oldest JDK you plan to support and then
您计划支持的最早的JDK，然后
distribute that instead so if you
分配它，所以如果你
actually want to use the features in
实际想使用中的功能
newer JDK it's a bit awkward and from
较新的JDK有点尴尬，
our perspective it slows adoption of the
我们的观点减缓了
new features of the JDK and we of course
JDK的新功能，我们当然
want people to use them so sometimes you
希望人们使用它们，所以有时您
can get around that by using reflection
可以通过反射来解决
to test for the new api's but that's
测试新的api，但这就是
kind of slow and awkward and the
有点缓慢和尴尬，
modularity features put in 9 make some
9中的模块化功能
shouldn't be used api's that are so
不应使用是如此的api
tempting to use some of those some not
试图使用其中一些而不是
somehow the star api is out of reach or
某种程度上，星型api无法到达或
harder to get to so what's the what's
很难到达所以这是什么
the alternative
替代方案
the alternative here is multi release
这里的替代方案是多版本
jar files in a multi release jar file
多版本jar文件中的jar文件
there's a shared common area across the
整个区域有一个公共区域
releases and then there directories in
发行，然后在
the meditative air iya that overload or
冥想的空气超载或
provide version specific class files to
提供特定于版本的类文件以
be used in particular JDK releases so
用于特定的JDK版本，因此
for instance there's a subdirectory for
例如，有一个子目录
JDK 9 and then you use those files when
JDK 9，然后在使用这些文件时
you're running on JDK 9 as opposed to
您在JDK 9上运行而不是
files you'd use on JDK 8 there are a few
您将在JDK 8上使用的文件有一些
things to do with this one thing you can
与这件事有关的事情，你可以
do is you can create a jar file that
你可以创建一个jar文件
acts as a regular old jar file on JDK 8
充当JDK 8上的常规旧jar文件
and earlier but acts as a new modular
和更早版本，但充当了新的模块化
jar file on JDK 9 you do that by having
JDK 9上的jar文件可以通过
the module info doc class files
模块信息文档类文件
available in the nine specific area you
在您指定的九个特定区域中可用
create these multi release jar files
创建这些多版本jar文件
using the jar command and we've updated
使用jar命令，我们已经更新
the other API is that consume jar files
另一个API是消耗jar文件
Java Java C and jar seiner to be multi
Java Java C和jar围网程序将变得更加多
release aware there's tooling support
意识到发布有工具支持
for creating multiple East jar files and
用于创建多个East jar文件，以及
and maven have documented ways to do
和Maven已经记录了方法
that and recently Trisha ghee posted a
，最近Trisha酥油发布了一个
demo code to create an altar release jar
演示代码创建祭坛释放罐
files and IntelliJ so you can check your
文件和IntelliJ，以便您可以检查
local to tool documentation for details
局部于工具文档以获取详细信息
next we start talking about the small
接下来我们开始谈论小
language changes that were made in JDK 9
JDK 9中进行的语言更改
back in JDK 7 we had a project called
在JDK 7中，我们有一个名为
project claim that added
项目声明，添加
a dozen small language changes for the
一打的小语言更改
platform and for three of those changes
平台以及其中的三处变化
we have some cleanup work we wanted to
我们有一些清理工作，我们想
do of work we couldn't quite finish by
我们无法完成的工作
the end of JDK 7 so those are the top
JDK 7的结束，所以这些是最重要的
three here project lambda which was
三个这里的项目lambda是
added in jdk 8 also had a few small
在jdk 8中添加的也有一些小
items to clean up so we kind of group
清理的物品，所以我们有点像
those together and also fix those in JDK
一起解决这些问题，并修复JDK中的问题
9 the first of these is safe varargs on
9其中第一个是安全的varargs
private instance methods
私有实例方法
so back in jdk 5 or 6 we could write
所以回到jdk 5或6，我们可以写
code like this we have a list of list of
这样的代码，我们有一个列表列表
strings and we want to help initialize
字符串，我们想帮助初始化
that using the arrays list platform
使用数组列表平台的
class so if you were careful about your
上课，所以如果你对自己的话很小心
compiler warnings you notice you get a
您注意到编译器警告
warning like this warning uncheck
像这样的警告取消警告
generic array creation for var X
var X的通用数组创建
parameter of the array saw Tesla's
阵列的参数看到特斯拉的
method so what's going on here this
方法，这是怎么回事
warning is mandated by the Java language
Java语言强制执行警告
specification and it's letting you know
规格，让您知道
that something bad might be happening
可能正在发生坏事
the something bad is called heap
不好的东西叫做堆
pollution which would be a violation of
可能违反的污染
Java's type constraints and if the
Java的类型约束以及
arrays dot s list method was malicious
数组点的列表方法是恶意的
and not implemented properly it could be
并没有正确实施
causing this kind of heat pollution
造成这种热污染
however in this case nothing bad
但是在这种情况下没有什么不好
actually happens already it's not as
实际发生的已经不是
listen the platform is not a malicious
听平台不是恶意的
method so this errors are false positive
方法，因此此错误为假阳性
it's uninformative so uninformative
它没有信息所以没有信息
warning messages aren't good
警告消息不好
so we addressed this problem back in jdk
所以我们在jdk中解决了这个问题
7 by adding the safe varargs annotation
7通过添加安全的varargs批注
type and the safe varargs annotation
类型和安全的varargs批注
type lets you tell the compiler that
类型可以让您告诉编译器
your varargs method is not in fact
您的varargs方法实际上不是
malicious and it shouldn't warn people
恶意的，它不应该警告人们
about it so this does two things both it
关于它，所以这同时做两件事
removes warnings when you declare the
声明以下内容时删除警告
large method and more importantly it
大方法，更重要的是
removes warnings every time people call
每次有人打电话时都会删除警告
the varargs method so we applied this
varargs方法，所以我们应用了
annotation to arrays that as lists and
注释为列表和数组的数组
the other appropriate message in the
另一个适当的消息
platform because of the design of
平台因为设计
annotations you can annotations are only
您可以注释的注释仅
in heret Adhan classes not interfaces or
在here Adhan类中不是接口或
methods therefore the safe varargs
因此，方法是安全的可变参数
annotation can only be used on methods
注释只能在方法上使用
that can't be overridden so what kinds
那不能被覆盖，那是什么样的
of methods can't be overridden final
的方法不能被覆盖
methods static methods also constructors
方法静态方法也是构造函数
which from a certain point of view are
从特定的角度来看
just very special static methods so are
只是非常特殊的静态方法
there any other
还有其他
kinds of message that can't be
不可能的那种消息
overridden there are private methods and
覆盖有私有方法和
we forgot about those ones in JDK 7 but
我们忘记了JDK 7中的那些，但是
now we've changed the specification in
现在我们已经更改了
implementation to also allow safer RS on
实施也允许更安全的RS
private methods so if you have such a
私人方法，如果您有这样的
method you can now use the annotation
现在可以使用注释的方法
line the other next change we made deals
排队我们进行交易的其他下一个变化
with the try with resources statement so
与try with resources语句一起使用
just as a quick refresher you have your
就像您快速上手一样
resource are being managed and behind
资源正在管理和落后
the scenes the compiler creates a
编译器创建的场景
implicit finally block for you to call
隐式的finally块供您调用
closed on the resource as long as it's
只要资源关闭
not null now in full disclosure the
现在不完全公开
actual code the compiler uses is a bit
编译器使用的实际代码有点
more complicated this is the actual to
更复杂的是实际
sugaring here the extra complex
在这里加糖额外的复杂
complexity is to give better exception
复杂性是为了给更好的例外
handling but we don't have to worry
处理，但我们不必担心
about this the compiler takes care of it
关于这一点，编译器会照顾它
for us so in JDK 7 the resource being
对我们来说，因此在JDK 7中
managed had to be a fresh variable
管理必须是一个新鲜的变量
associate with the tribe earth resources
与部落地球资源相关联
statement that wasn't the initial
并非最初的陈述
proposal however originally you could
建议，但是最初您可以
use any expression with the right type
使用任何具有正确类型的表达式
which was Auto closable meaning closed
这是自动关闭的，表示已关闭
method was there but we found there's a
方法在那里，但我们发现有一个
problem using that so let's say we
使用这个问题，所以我们说
initialize our resource R to a new
将资源R初始化为新的
resource object and then within the try
资源对象，然后在try内
block we make our point to a different
阻止，我们提出了不同的观点
resource object now we come to the end
资源对象到此结束
of the try block and what are we
的尝试块，我们是什么
supposed to do which object is supposed
应该做哪个对象
to get its closed method called well we
得到它的封闭方法叫我们
decided we didn't want to have to solve
决定我们不想解决
this problems and the way we decide not
这个问题和我们决定不的方式
to solve it was to require a final
解决它是需要最终的
require that new final variable as part
要求将新的最终变量作为一部分
of the drivers resources statement but
驱动程序资源声明，但
this was actually a little bit stricter
这实际上有点严格
than would need to be so if we already
如果我们已经
know that the some resource variable is
知道一些资源变量是
final or effectively final why do we
最终或有效最终我们为什么
have to declare a new fresh final or
必须声明一个新的新鲜的决赛或
variable to take care of it there's
变量来照顾它
really no reason to do that and that is
真的没有理由这样做，那是
indeed the change now we've made in JDK
确实是我们现在在JDK中所做的更改
9 so if you already have a final
9所以如果您已经有决赛
variable you don't have to make a new
您不必重新创建变量
one you can just reuse the one you have
你可以重复使用一个
so it makes it try our three sources
因此，它尝试了我们的三个来源
statements a bit more concise
声明更加简洁
Dimond in anonymous classes that's the
匿名类中的Dimond是
next feature we'll be talking about
我们将要讨论的下一个功能
so back before JDK 7 if you had your
回到JDK 7之前，如果您有
list of map of strings integers you'd
您想要的字符串整数映射列表
clear the variable and then in the
清除变量，然后在
constructor call say ArrayList you'd
构造函数调用说ArrayList
have to repeat list of map of string of
必须重复的字符串映射列表
integer that was a bit for both so now
整数，两者都有点
you can just have the diamond and the
你可以拥有钻石和
compiler will infer those type arguments
编译器将推断出这些类型参数
for you
为了你
this was very effective at removing the
这对于消除
need for explicit constructor type
需要显式构造函数类型
arguments however due to a bad
但是由于不好而引起的争论
worst-case interaction we have to forbid
我们必须禁止的最坏情况的交互
using diamond when you were using
在使用钻石时
anonymous inner classes the problem is
匿名内部类的问题是
in the worst case the compiler could
在最坏的情况下，编译器可能
infer something called a non de notable
推断出一种不显眼的东西
type
类型
this is a type outside of the type
这是类型之外的类型
system we can use as programmers but
我们可以用作程序员的系统，但
exists inside the compiler and the
存在于编译器内部，并且
problem is if you have an anonymous
问题是如果您有匿名者
class that needs a class file and part
需要一个类文件和部分的类
of the information in the class file it
类文件中的信息
needs is the type arguments and if you
需要的是类型参数，如果您
have a non notable type inferred it's
有一个非明显的类型推断是
outside what you can write in the class
在课堂上可以写的东西之外
file so that's bad so in other cases
文件，所以不好，在其他情况下
though if you get a D notable type infer
但是如果您得到D值得注意的类型推断
one of the normal types we usually deal
我们通常处理的一种普通类型
with that could be represented in the
可以在
class file so we noted that we had to
类文件，所以我们注意到我们必须
forbid Dimond and anonymous classes
禁止Dimond和匿名类
working together at all in seven but
七个人一起工作
when we were finishing up a project coin
当我们完成项目硬币时
we said it's feasible that in the future
我们说将来可行
we might remove this restriction in the
我们可能会在
case when you get a D notable type and
当您得到D显着类型和
you avoid that worst case and that is
您避免了最坏的情况，那就是
indeed in fact what we've now done in
实际上，实际上我们现在所做的
JDK 9 so as long as you don't get that
JDK 9，只要您不明白
worst case outcome you can use diamond
可以使用钻石的最坏情况
with anonymous classes too in JDK 7 a
在JDK 7 a中也具有匿名类
diamond got let us get rid of about 90%
钻石让我们摆脱了大约90％
of the explicit constructor type
显式构造函数类型
arguments and we feel with the this
论点，我们对此感到
cleanup for the notable types we can
清理我们可以注意到的类型
address much of the remaining 10% we've
解决我们剩下的10％中的大部分
had good experience using this feature
在使用此功能方面经验丰富
in the JDK codebase it's let us get rid
在JDK代码库中，它让我们摆脱了
of hundreds of additional explicit
数百个其他显式的
constructor arguments in our code next
接下来的代码中的构造函数参数
two features are from project lambda so
两个功能来自lambda项目，因此
underscore is no longer an identifier
下划线不再是标识符
name back when lambda is added in JDK
在JDK中添加lambda时重新命名
eight you could use underscore as the
八个，您可以使用下划线作为
the parameter name for a lambda that was
Lambda的参数名称是
to avoid confusion with some features
避免与某些功能混淆
from other programming languages like
来自其他编程语言，例如
wunderbar from Scout Scala Java Steve
Scout Scala Java Steve的wunderbar
started noting though that if you're
开始注意到，如果你是
using underscore in other circumstances
在其他情况下使用下划线
as a data file you might not be able to
作为数据文件，您可能无法
use them in the future and now that
在将来使用它们，现在
future has arrived you can no longer use
未来已经到来，您不能再使用
underscore as a variable name in a as a
在变量中以下划线作为变量名
jetty k9 so this is not our usual policy
码头k9，所以这不是我们通常的政策
but why are of keeping code compiling
但是为什么要保持代码编译
but why are we making this change
但是我们为什么要进行此更改
well we think there's better use for the
好吧，我们认为有更好的用途
syntactic real estate of underscore a
下划线a的句法不动产
single underscore for a variable name
变量名称下划线
and that work is being discussed in a
这项工作正在讨论中
future JEP JEP 3 or 2 lambda left overs
未来的JEP JEP 3或2剩余的lambda
which is part of project amber one of
这是琥珀项目之一的一部分
our ongoing projects in open JDK finally
我们在开放式JDK中正在进行的项目终于
we have a private interface methods
我们有一个私有接口方法
another part of project lambda in 8 was
在8中，lambda项目的另一部分是
adding default methods that interfaces
添加接口的默认方法
these are methods on interfaces that
这些是接口上的方法
have code so they're not the abstract
有代码，所以它们不是抽象的
methods we had before and at the VM
虚拟机之前和之后使用的方法
level it's possible to have private
级别可以有私人
methods on interfaces in 8 these were
8个接口上的方法是
necessary to implement lambdas however
但是实现lambda是必需的
you couldn't do that in the source
您无法在源代码中做到这一点
language and now in Java 9 you can you
语言，现在在Java 9中，您可以
can have both private static methods on
可以同时使用两个私有静态方法
your interfaces as well as private
您的界面以及私人界面
instance methods so what you do with
实例方法，所以您要做什么
these methods you can use them as helper
这些方法，您可以将它们用作帮助者
methods for the other default method you
其他默认方法的方法
have any interface the public method so
有任何公共方法的接口
this is again very very convenient to
这再次非常非常方便
have once you start adding default
一旦您开始添加默认值
methods to your own to your own
您自己的方法
interfaces so you may have heard at the
介面，所以您可能在
keynote earlier about the new six-month
关于新的六个月的主题演讲
release cating cadence were
释放饮食节奏
transitioning to for the JDK one of the
过渡到JDK之一
benefits we think will have from this
我们认为将从中受益
release cadence is that these sort of
释放节奏是这样的
small language changes we delivered more
较小的语言更改，我们提供了更多
quickly and they won't be backed up
很快，他们将不会被备份
behind a large I which changed before so
在我改变之前的大我背后
we're looking forward to that to get
我们期待着得到
these sorts of small language cleanups
这类小语言清理
available to developers sooner their
可供开发人员尽快使用
number changes we made to the language
我们对语言进行的数字更改
in related to deprecation the first of
与弃用有关
those is deprecation and imports like
那是折旧和进口像
any old code base that's been around for
任何已经存在的旧代码库
a while at times we had some technical
有时我们有一些技术
debt in the JDK
JDK中的债务
and in years past we've had several
在过去的几年中，我们有几个
hundred deprecation warnings in the
百次弃用警告
build of the JDK itself now these
JDK本身的构建现在这些
warnings are again mandated by the
警告再次由
language specification and there's three
语言规范，其中有三个
ways to resolve those deprecation
解决这些折旧的方法
warnings you can remove use of the
警告，您可以删除对
deprecated elements that's preferred but
不推荐使用的元素，但
you can't always do that you can
你不能总是那样做
propagate the deprecated annotation to
将不推荐使用的注释传播到
the youth sites that's not very good
青年网站不是很好
either because now you're making more of
要么是因为现在您正在赚更多
your code deprecated so if you can't do
您的代码已弃用，因此如果您无法执行
either of those you can suppress the
那些你可以压制
warnings to let the compiler know to not
使编译器不知道的警告
warn you about that anymore so let's say
再次警告您，让我们说
you had your client library on JDK 5
您在JDK 5上拥有客户端库
through 8 and it was used some
到8
deprecated type in the JDK you compile
您编译的JDK中不推荐使用的类型
this and you get your duplication
这，你得到你的重复
warning so I figure no problem I have to
警告，所以我认为没有问题
keep using this type so I'll just put
继续使用这种类型，所以我就把
that suppress warnings annotation right
禁止警告注释的权利
at the top of the class and this will
在全班最高，这将
take care of everything
照顾好一切
right now unfortunately if you run the
现在不幸的是，如果您运行
compiler again you'll notice you still
再次编译，您仍然会注意到
have a deprecation morning so what's
有一个过时的早晨，那是什么
going on here the warning you're getting
在这里继续警告您
now isn't from any of the code of the
现在不是来自任何代码
class it's actually from the import
类实际上是从导入
statement at the top and this is
顶部的声明，这是
mandated by the Java language
由Java语言授权
specification you might say well that's
您可能会说的规范是
not a problem I'll just apply another
没问题，我只用另一个
suppress warnings annotation that
禁止显示警告注释
doesn't work either you syntactically
在语法上你也不起作用
you can't allow that so while this
你不能那样做
warning may be very thorough and well
警告可能非常彻底而且很好
intentioned it's really unhelpful if all
意图如果真的全部都没有帮助
the uses all the other uses of the
该用途的所有其他用途
deprecated type can be covered by the
不推荐使用的类型可以由
suppress warnings annotation it seems a
禁止显示警告注释
bit silly to force you to do something
有点傻逼你去做某事
like use the fully qualified name of the
例如使用
deprecated type everywhere just to avoid
不推荐使用的类型，只是为了避免
this warning so we decided that was a
这个警告，所以我们认为这是一个
little little unnecessary and we've
一点点不必要，我们已经
updated the language specification to
将语言规范更新为
not require a deprecation warning in
不需要中的弃用警告
this location and because of this
这个位置，因为这个
language change it is now tractable to
语言更改现在很容易处理
clear a code base of deprecation
清除弃用的代码库
warnings and we have an existence proof
警告，我们有存在证明
of that by clearing the Java based
通过清除基于Java的
module and the Java desktop module
模块和Java桌面模块
amongst other modules in the JDK of
在JDK的其他模块中
deprecation warnings so if you have such
弃用警告，所以如果您有这样的警告
warnings in your own code base I
您自己的代码库中的警告
encourage you to look into them and try
鼓励您调查一下并尝试
to try to get them under control now
尽力控制他们
there's a bit more to say about
还有更多要说的
deprecation there's been
过时了
here's some confusion about deprecation
这是关于弃用的一些困惑
what does it mean is it deprecated
这是什么意思？
because it's harmful is it deprecated
因为它是有害的，不建议使用
because it's going away and if it's
因为它要消失了，如果
deprecated because it's going away well
已过时，因为它进展顺利
I haven't you JDK guys removed things
我不是吗JDK家伙删除了东西
yet so we wanted to give more
但我们想提供更多
information in this situation and we did
在这种情况下的信息，我们做到了
that by enhancing the information
通过增强信息
available in the deprecation annotation
在弃用注释中可用
type there are two new methods added one
键入添加了两种新方法
of those is a predicate for removal that
这些是删除predicate，
defaults to false so if something is
默认为false，所以如果有
deprecated for removal true that means
弃用移除true表示
in some relatively near future platform
在一些相对较近的平台上
release we plan to remove it you also
发布我们计划将其删除
can add a string for the since release
可以为之后的版本添加字符串
that something was first deprecated
最初不推荐使用的东西
we've updated the deprecation
我们更新了弃用
annotations in the core platform to have
核心平台中的注释具有
this for removal information and their
这用于删除信息及其
supporting updates made in language
支持语言更新
specification java c and java talk also
规范java c和java talk也
there's a new static analysis tool in
有一个新的静态分析工具
the JDK called J deeper scan that
JDK称为J更深层扫描
analyzes class files and rar files for
分析类文件和rar文件以获取
the use of api's that were deprecated in
在api中已弃用的api的使用
the jdk so we have how do these
JDK，所以我们有这些
deprecations including for removal
弃用，包括去除
deprecations so you don't have to
弃用，所以您不必
recompile your code though to find out
重新编译代码以找出答案
though if your jar files are affected by
但是如果您的jar文件受到
it you can just run j deeper scan on
它可以运行j更深的扫描
your jar files instead and you can find
而是您的jar文件，您可以找到
out what's going on next we'll talk
知道接下来会发生什么
about some of the library updates that
关于一些库更新
went on in the release first of these
首先在这些发行中
was the new version string the one dot
是新版本的字符串一个点
in 1.8 and 1.7 and so forth has gone
在1.8和1.7中等等
away so if you run a version on your new
离开，所以如果您在新版本上运行版本
download of JDK 9 and it'll just say
JDK 9的下载，它只会说
it's version 9 and it's you know build 9
这是版本9，您知道版本9
+ 1 81 don't get too used to this though
+ 1 81虽然不太习惯
because the version scheme will likely
因为版本方案可能
change again instead of JDK 10 we might
再次更改而不是JDK 10，我们可能
have 18.3 maybe it'll be X or JDK a
有18.3，也许是X或JDK
we'll see in the coming once what the
我们将在未来一次看到
final name is but we won't the 1 dot
最终名称是，但我们不会用1点
won't be coming back so if you have
不会再回来的，所以如果你有
tooling that checks for this it'll have
检查它的工具
to be updated if you use Java to talk to
如果您使用Java与之交谈，则需要更新
native OS processes there's some
本机操作系统进程中有一些
additional API elements to control those
其他API元素来控制那些
more directly including getting the pid'
更直接地包括获取pid'
a few interesting features related to
一些有趣的功能
strings the first of these is compact
琴弦中的第一个是紧凑的
strings where
字符串在哪里
without any user intervention if your
如果您的用户没有任何用户干预
string doesn't require any of the high
字符串不需要任何高
bytes to be nonzero it'll use a one byte
个字节为非零，它将使用一个字节
per character representation as opposed
每个字符表示相对
to the old one care one car per
到老一关一车
character of representation if you do
如果你有代表性的话
need the high bytes that it'll use two
需要使用两个高字节
bytes instead so this can give you a
字节代替，这样可以给你一个
better memory usage for your
更好的内存使用
applications especially ones using
应用程序，尤其是使用
strings and you don't have to update
字符串，您不必更新
your application in a way to take
您的应用程序采用
advantage of that the second feature in
第二个功能的优势
destroy into five string concatenation
销毁成五个字符串串联
is a good example of a feature that
是该功能的一个很好的例子
crosses all of the VM the language and
跨所有VM的语言
well as the compiler like Java see it's
像Java这样的编译器看到了
a very common operation in the Java
Java中非常常见的操作
platform to concatenate strings together
将字符串连接在一起的平台
Java C happens to do this usually with
Java C碰巧通常会这样做
string builder calls and then the VM has
字符串生成器调用，然后虚拟机具有
to notice this idioms used by Java seen
注意Java所使用的这个惯用法
other compilers and kind of try to
其他编译器和尝试
optimize that accordingly so since this
相应地进行优化，因此
is such a common operation instead a new
如此常见的操作而不是新的
stable entry point was created in Java
稳定的入口点是用Java创建的
lieing invoke and the intended user of
说谎调用和目标用户
this API is not programmers but it's
这个API不是程序员，而是
compilers like Java C so there's a very
Java C之类的编译器，因此
straightforward way compilers can take
编译器可以采取的直接方式
advantage of this to communicate with
与之沟通的优势
the VM and lets the VM have easily have
虚拟机，让虚拟机轻松拥有
know the semantics of the code and
知道代码的语义，并且
generate faster code as a result so this
结果生成更快的代码，因此
effectively adds a new JVM capability
有效地添加了新的JVM功能
without having to define a new bike code
无需定义新的自行车代码
there are a number of updates made to
有许多更新
the security libraries the general
安全库一般
security policies who want the JDK to be
希望JDK成为安全策略的人
secure out-of-the-box
开箱即用
I mean who wanted to restrict broken or
我的意思是谁想限制损坏或
weak cryptographic algorithms and
弱密码算法和
protocols now as a cryptographers become
如今，作为密码学家的协议成为
more clever and computers become faster
更聪明，计算机变得更快
which algorithms are weaker broken
哪些算法较弱
varies so Oracle's published a crypto
变化，因此甲骨文发布了一个加密货币
roadmap for the JDK where we announce
我们宣布的JDK路线图
ahead of time when certain algorithms
提前某些算法
and protocols will be deprecated or
和协议将被弃用或
removed from the default set because of
由于以下原因而从默认设置中删除
those reasons on that is a document that
这些原因是文件
does get updated as a situation change
确实随着情况的变化而更新
if you highlights this to you at the
如果您在
Security api's in nine by this secure by
安全API的安全性由9
default policy the default key thises
默认策略默认密钥this
for RSA were increased and so forth also
RSA增加了，等等
certificates with weak keys are no
密钥较弱的证书为否
longer accepted by default there are
默认情况下不再接受
some system settings you can use to
您可以用来进行一些系统设置
still have those certificates accepted
仍然接受那些证书
if you need them my colleague Sean
如果您需要他们，我的同事肖恩
Mullan gave a talk about making the JDK
Mullan发表了有关制作JDK的演讲
more secure that covers the JDK nine
更安全，涵盖了JDK 9
security lives features in more detail
安全生活功能更详细
and the video for that talk is already
该演讲的视频已经
up from the conference there are also
从会议开始还有
updates to the client libraries and FX
客户端库和FX的更新
in the release like other parts of the
像其他版本一样
JDK the FX code base most was modulized
JDK FX代码库最模块化
they were updates to graphic support in
他们是对图形支持的更新
various in various ways a few notable
各种方式各不相同
projects the marlin graphics render
投影马林图形渲染
replaced the previous Pisces and ductus
取代了以前的双鱼座和导管
renderers this removed one of the major
渲染器删除了其中一个主要
remaining behavioral differences between
剩余的行为差异
Oracle JDK and open JDK so now there you
Oracle JDK并打开JDK，所以现在就在那里
know the JK's are using the same
知道JK正在使用相同的
implementation code in both
两者中的实现代码
circumstances and for the photographer's
情况和摄影师的情况
who also used Java there's now support
谁也使用过Java，现在有支持
for TIFF images including the exif
用于TIFF图像，包括exif
metadata there are a number of talks
元数据有很多话题
about the client libraries at JavaOne
关于JavaOne上的客户端库
and you can see them listed here few of
您可以在此处看到其中列出的一些
miscellaneous library treats as well
其他图书馆也一样
first of these is convenience factory
首先是便利工厂
methods so how many times have you
方法，你有多少次
written code like this right at the end
最后写这样的代码
you want to have an unmodifiable set of
您想要一组不可修改的
strings so what you have to do today you
字符串，所以你今天要做的是
you know have your half set you call add
你知道你已经设置好一半了吗？
add add and then you have the collection
添加添加，然后您有集合
set unmodifiable wrapper that's a bit
设置一些不可修改的包装器
verbose for a simple operation so there
冗长的操作简单，所以
are other things you can do you can use
你可以做的其他事情就是
code like this instead where you
这样的代码，而不是你
initialize the hash set using arrays dot
使用数组点初始化哈希集
as list and then you wrap that that's
作为列表，然后将其包装
still a bit long there's also the double
还有些长，还有一倍
brace it IAM which we won't even show
支持IAM，我们什至不会显示
that some people use so but you don't
一些人使用的，但是你不
have to do this anymore in jdk 9 now you
现在必须在jdk 9中再做一次
can just write this
可以写这个
set that off and then what you want to
将其关闭，然后您想要
initialize the set to and what you get
将集合初始化为以及您得到什么
out of this is a unmodifiable set of
这是一组不可修改的
strings so this idiom is supported on
字符串，因此支持该惯用法
sets list in maps and it approximates
设置地图中的列表，它近似
the functionality of collection a little
收集功能
collection little rules collection the
收集小规矩
rules were one of the features we looked
规则是我们看过的功能之一
at for project coin and JDK 7 but we
在项目硬币和JDK 7，但我们
didn't have time to do this is a good
没时间做这是一个好习惯
way to get most of that functionality at
获得大部分功能的方法
a small fraction of the complexity to
复杂度的一小部分
the platform now we mentioned that the
现在我们提到的平台
hash that thought iteration order and
散列该思想迭代顺序并
people relying on that unknowingly these
人们在不知不觉中依靠这些
new collections will discourage that by
新的收藏将不鼓励
having a random iteration order sets and
具有随机的迭代顺序集
sets of maps not for the list so every
多套地图不在清单中，所以每一个
time you create these you'll get a
创建这些内容时，您将获得一个
different iteration order which will
不同的迭代顺序
make it more difficult to rely on the
使其更难以依靠
iteration order when you're when you're
当您在的时候，迭代顺序
using them and for more information my
使用它们并了解更多信息
colleague stuart marx gave a talk about
斯图尔特·马克思同事发表了有关
this feature earlier this morning if you
如果您今天早上有此功能，
use Java util objects for common
使用Java util对象进行通用
functionality we did add some methods
我们确实添加了一些方法
there as well some additional null
还有一些其他的null
checking in index checking methods some
检入索引检查方法一些
of these have intrinsic support from the
其中有来自
VM few odds and ends I am interested in
VM我感兴趣的一些零散
math so we've had the fuse multiply add
数学，所以我们有保险丝乘加
method add it's at the platform this is
方法添加它在平台上是
a hardware instruction that's becoming
越来越多的硬件指令
more and more common it allows you to do
越来越多的它可以让你做
two floating point operations with only
仅有两个浮点运算
one rounding error and it's good for
一个舍入错误，这对
some numerical tricks and this again has
一些数字技巧，这又有
hardware support on many platforms that
许多平台上的硬件支持
we have intrinsic for those also there
我们也有内在的
are some array comparisons for likes
一些喜欢的数组比较
graphic array those have also been
图形阵列也已经
intrinsic ID and if you're interested in
固有ID以及您是否有兴趣
things like var handles which is a
像var handles这样的东西
common for a concurrent programming
并发编程常见
using things like C++ Atomics those have
使用像C ++ Atomics这样的东西
been added to the platform as well and
也被添加到平台中
my colleague Paul Santos gave a talk
我的同事保罗·桑托斯（Paul Santos）发表了演讲
about those at a conference the JVM LS
关于会议上的JVM LS
conference in 2015 there's some other
2015年的会议还有其他
survey talks about JDK 9 at the
关于JDK 9的调查
conference if you want to hear other
会议，如果你想听其他
people's takes about what's what's good
人们对什么才是好事的看法
there the first of these JDK 9 hidden
这些JDK 9的第一个隐藏了
gems focuses more on the VM
gems专注于VM
performance aspects of the platform in
平台的性能方面
the video for that is also up online
该视频也在线播放
already
已经
so in summary JDK 9 was a very large
所以总而言之，JDK 9很大
release we've made some fundamental
发布，我们做了一些基本
development changes with modularity but
开发随着模块化而变化，但是
the changes weren't limited in
更改不限于
modularity we also finished long-planned
模块化我们也完成了长期计划
improvements to the language from
语言的改进来自
project coin in lambda and if you're
在lambda中投影硬币，如果您
interested in following future
有兴趣跟随未来
developments you can do that in open JDK
您可以在开放的JDK中做到这一点
and you can download the JDK 9 bits to
您可以将JDK 9位下载到
try out now so with that I think I have
现在尝试一下，我想我有
time for one or two questions right so
时间是一两个问题吧
the question is how does the - - release
问题是--发布如何
flag interact with - source and mask
标志与-来源和遮罩互动
target and the answer is Java C gives an
目标，答案是Java C提供了一个
error if you try to do both so you can
如果您尝试同时执行这两个操作，则会出错
do one or the other you either have to
做一个或另一个你必须
do - - release where takes care of
做--释放照顾的地方
everything or you can use the source and
一切，或者您可以使用源和
target Flags explicitly the tools will
目标标志明确地将工具
have to change the support it yes all
必须改变支持，是的，所有
right well I think I said thank you for
好吧，我想我说谢谢
coming you today
今天来你
[Applause]
[掌声]